Ela: To be honest, er there are quite a few things that I like, er that I prefer to do on my own.
For instance, when I am reading or studying or just trying to get things done, I,
I value peace and quiet. Er, I find it much easier to, focus when there isn’t anyone around to,
to interrupt my train of thought.
I sometimes, quite often actually, er, travel alone.
I like travelling alone because I like feeling independent.
Er, and also, I’m, when I travel alone, I’m more open to, er, new experiences.
I notice more, er, and, and also, I travel at my own pace.
Begoña: There are things that I prefer to do alone, such as going shopping.
And when I go shopping, I sometimes find it quite difficult to make up my mind.
So I prefer to be alone and not to have anybody waiting for me.
That way, I have time to decide what to do and what to buy.
Geoffrey: I absolutely love watching movies all on my own.
It’s the best thing in the world, lying on my sofa in the living room, watching television,
nobody around and nobody interfering, nobody talking over the actors.
And I can watch the movie as I please, I can pause when I want, I can go back.
I can rewind to watch some bits. And yeah, that’s the best way to enjoy a really good movie.
Ross: I prefer to work alone.
Um, I know that might sound odd, but when it comes,
a lot of my work revolves around stuff like video editing, as well as teaching.
And I’ve, well you’re in front of a computer, basically.
Um, some people like to do that type of thing with others who kind of comment
on their work as they’re doing it and give them advice, and that’s great. I, I agree with that.
But I’ve always felt like I work better and faster when I’m working on my own.
Um, I tend to be more imaginative and creative, and I think that’s because I’m, you know,
you’re not self-conscious about what other people think when you’re working away on your own,
you’re just getting on with it.